an aided stream on repay it sings the phone buddy's there when it rings the sky
i need my coffee
the last night though it was fun i just like i don't have memory of it really i remember
getting really drunk and i think i had four drinks and that's like way more than i usually have
and then something about christine kicking me off of money for 20s panel and ghost wrote me like
Going what happened? Was that you?
Who else would it be who else?
Anyway, so yeah, I got the energy going up today
What's gonna say? Okay, um
Let me see
apologize. Oh, yeah, so
There was an incident like oh, we're a mod a mod
Time someone out for like 30 seconds. Hi brave little toaster. How are you?
Yeah, and and then that person got mad and there wasn't really a reason
for
Getting that person mad. I mean, it's like and so, you know, there's misunderstanding about it
And you know, I think we're all adults. We can all work out. It's not a big the biggest deal
I mean, it's like I can say is you know, sorry people were offended. I just gotta like, you know, try to keep you're doing well
All's good good. I just gotta keep this show
You know, it's like fun. It's like safe for everybody and and so it wasn't like anything personal against anybody
And it's like a promise don't get deleted. I don't know. I think I that's why I have people or mods
But and then it's like the mod but it can't be like modding with people's feelings
It has to be fair and like maybe protecting the show is the first priority rather than like settling
Vandettas and so it's all good and uh, you know, hope everyone can come back and stuff and uh
Not you know, you know, there's other issues going on too, but people can go where they want to go. It's fine
It's like, you know, I don't care
But yeah, so I mean just
But they'll come in they'll say oh my god, there's nobody here. I mean, it's like it's like they're really just obvious trolls
So numbs they like, you know, you know that there was a great video
salmon was playing this morning at Kate like sobbing and it's like, you know
Not like it's like a good thing. She's sobbing, but it's like it won't maybe nice to see it's an emotional vulnerability in that woman
You know, it's like because she's so been so heartless and cold to me, but you know
But I was gonna say about that, you know, you should just have a heart and you have this video coming out soon though
new cartoon
For you guys will love it. It's like this only six second preview, but here you go. Oh
Hold on. I need to take that
Okay, here we go. Try again
Okay, what do you think? Oh, I guess three people didn't like that
Three people really didn't like that. Okay. Well
Still the Sam and Cartier. Oh, everyone like that. Oh, I'm so sorry
So sorry
Well, I don't know maybe off to cancel it won't be popular show. I mean it's like I'll see like
I guess I just fed everybody. Well, I guess well, yeah
I don't see any people like leaving when like, you know, he like puts up fake photos of me
I mean, that's actually just like a
My he looks better in that car. Wait, she's see the original footage. I made that from but yeah
Y'all three wind a little bit cuz I don't want to scare everyone away. I guess I scared people with his real appearance like
Okay
Well, let's see. Yeah, so that was my that was my apology. I guess I mean, it's like it wasn't good enough, but
I'm tired. I'm tired. I'm tired. And so, you know, hopefully that was good enough.
Look what I have. I have a huge thing of like sour punch things, but then I think they really upset
my stomach. They're really good. They're probably my favorite candy. I have a whole tub of them.
And uh, I don't know, you're doing well. Look at a kicker.
So yeah, that's not bad to say hi, but no one's really talking. It gets like a kind of awkward
just focus I just feel like too much focus on me even though it's just focus should be on me I just
don't have like you know I'm like more conversationalist and so it's like sitting here in silence it's
like a little bit more difficult but anyway I just to come and say hi and stuff it's good
and new cartoon coming out can't wait for you guys to see it it's gonna be great freaking
Okay. Should I just go? I can go. I want to talk. Okay. And you need to check a few things.
Yeah, maybe I shouldn't have. Okay, or maybe I'll just wait a little bit.
Yeah, keep it in a psyche. Trilogy continues. I have a few more to make. I think I did one
through seven. And so that's pretty exciting. I mean, these are just kind of to educate people
Bring into life in a certain way that it hasn't even been brought to life before I don't think in so I think it's groundbreaking
But you know, you know your own opinions but here
No Titan King had ever captured. What is mother captured here. Golden feathers fill the throne like autumn leaves before each one cares with you.
Do you want to watch some bully cats? I think my cat videos are usually not.
I'm in a dangerous zone. Don't bite the baby.
Those intense eyes outside the window say, you're living in my territory now.
Unbelievable.
You have to hold it in the water.
This is happening.
Uh-uh.
Crap and stewing.
They're definitely planning their revenge
for this terrible inconvenience.
Uh-uh.
Crickshanks.
Leave her alone, dude.
She doesn't like it.
Every tap says,
relaxation denied.
I run this household starting with your patience.
That's you can hit me this tiny cat has turned into an immovable obstacle for the brave giant dog
This is the look of a cat deciding whether you deserve forgiveness or permanent disaster
Literally walking all over you to assert dominance. No personal space
This muscular cat is not just drinking. It's asserting dominance with splash attacks
That little cat just proofs eyes, doesn't matter when you're the true boss.
It's always wrong, yeah, are you?
Put it in the bag.
No, I'm not. You were still over there.
That cat just claimed the dog as its property with a territorial headlamp.
don't think so. Are you loving these adorable acts of cat bullying? Let me know your thoughts
in the comments below.
Don't forget to like and is it possible to define the single best stock trade every single day?
I'm Emily Turner award-winning journalist and host of unfiltered finance YouTube channel
One of the experts that I've interviewed recently says that he built a tool that does exactly that and he says you could even try it for free
Click the link in this video right now to join a special presentation and learn how to unlock
30 days of full access for zero costs. Not even a credit card is required.
The tool uses a proprietary formula to scan the entire market and identifies only the strongest
candidates in real time. Then, incredibly, it searches through millions of option combinations
to actually build the best trade for you right there.
the link below to watch the presentation where Nate attempts to prove there really is a best
The boss cat is not amused by the tiny news.
Oh, this is not where they are.
So much for a warm welcome.
This is not where they are.
I quickly reminded the raccoon who's in charge with a swift.
The villainous cat is still plotting its break-in.
Those eyes are full of mischief.
Cat's playful bite is a clear message.
I own this arm now, human.
The power of a cat's stare, successfully claiming the comfy chair without a paw lift.
Warning hot. No, thank you. No, thank you total domination
That cat is literally pinning down its victim asserting its furry superiority
So coming soon some new cartoon I'm working on I'm looking to recognize
Protagonists, but you might know them. Okay, I need to take a nap
Later. I love you guys. Thank you so much